<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Myanmar Night Life</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="share_image_transition">share_image_transition</string>

    <string name="desc">Are you looking somewhere to have fun at night so that you can relax your mind loading with works, studying, and so many pressures in day time?
Is it difficult to find those places in no time?
No! It is very easy to find those places that can give you fun at night with our app “Myanmar Nightlife”
Life is short, so give sometime to have fun your mind.</string>

    <string name="owaydesc">We offer a selection of on-demand services at the touch of your mobile device to suit your needs.
A Oway Ride is one that is Safe, Certain and Fast, the 3 key pillars that we focus on.
App features include live tracking, receive information of your driver’s details, strict driver selection and screening processes and receive booking confirmation within a minute</string>

    <string name="hellocabsdesc">Get a safe and reliable ride in minutes with Hellocabs.No reservations, standing on road.24/7 service available.
Travel with confidence knowing that Hellocabs invests in safety training for drivers, security and convenience.
How to Hellocabs :
1. Download the app for free and register your account
2. Start booking! The app auto-detects your location for pick up.</string>

    <string name="indriverdesc">inDriver is a popular mobile app connecting drivers and passengers directly! It is a comfortable up-to-date solution for commuting in urban environment with tons of advantages.
SAVE MONEY
Passengers set fares by themselves! They decide which fare is affordable and reasonable for their rides. Usually the average cost of rides with inDriver is 30-50% cheaper than when taking traditional taxi cabs.

</string>

</resources>
